<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[What's Neat Today]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[What's Neat Today]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/whats-neat-today/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2016 16:39:29 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/whats-neat-today/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Interview: Artist Ryan McGinness on Designing for Hennessy]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Interview: Artist Ryan McGinness on Designing for Hennessy</h1><p>Despite the fact that he works across multiple artistic mediums, it's very easy to discern the work of NYC-based artist Ryan McGinness. In addition to his iconic symbol-driven body of work, his experimental Instagram and the depths of his oftentimes ornate paintings, McGinness recently took to designing a special limited edition bottle for luxury cognac brand Hennessy.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/b0177dec01e85895d69f554c2d73fc2a73857261.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.coolhunting.com/design/ryan-mcginness-hennessy-bottle</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">d91681fc-c604-4a72-9331-da7038b0b804</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2016 16:39:14 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Assignment of a Lifetime: Riding in a U-2 Spy Plane at the Edge of Space]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Assignment of a Lifetime: Riding in a U-2 Spy Plane at the Edge of Space</h1><p>Back in 2010, San Francisco-based photographer Christopher Michel received a once-in-a-lifetime photo assignment from the US Navel Institute: to ride in the back seat of a U-2 spy plane at the "edge of space." At the plane's cruising and intelligence-gathering altitude of 70,000 feet above the ground, temperatures outside the plane fall to 70 degrees below zero.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/04f6c0633f5a485f90dde99e96cd653a67f86bd6.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://petapixel.com/2015/05/24/assignment-of-a-lifetime-riding-in-a-u-2-spy-plane-at-the-edge-of-space/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">03f11c72-2bd5-4ed4-9ee4-a8d952310469</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2016 16:39:14 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sleep Beneath the Stars in the Italian Alps | Travel Away]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Sleep Beneath the Stars in the Italian Alps | Travel Away</h1><p>A brainchild of local hotelier Raniero Campigotto, Starlight Room Dolomites is a mobile glass-encased bedroom tucked away in the picturesque Italian Alps, 20 km from the swanky ski resort of Cortina d'Ampezzo. Perched at an altitude of 2,055 meters, the secluded cabin rewards those who brave the climb up with marvelous mountain views by day and pollution-free starry skies by night.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/0895eb60736ea7b14be4c5d3a67591db4746a3c6.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://travelaway.me/sleep-beneath-stars-italian-alps/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">794dfc67-5e79-4782-af21-a5f40e8a3de5</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2016 16:39:14 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Colorado's Woody Creek Distillers]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Colorado's Woody Creek Distillers</h1><p>Only last week a panel of expert judges convened for the annual San Francisco World Spirits Competition-arguably the most prestigious and analytical booze assembling in the States. While the complete results won't be formally announced until 4 April, it's already known that Colorado's independently owned Woody Creek Distillers (located just a 20-minute drive from downtown Aspen) won double gold for one of their newer releases: a tasty small-batch Colorado Straight Rye.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/b64dca9b02fd08fb329890c39fa2430abff82993.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.coolhunting.com/food-drink/woody-creek-distillers-colorado</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">16fbb800-1ecb-46c8-8e2d-0f1a98a2c02c</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2016 16:39:14 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Remembering Prince: What The Purple One Can Teach You About Creativity]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Remembering Prince: What The Purple One Can Teach You About Creativity</h1><p>Join Entrepreneur and today's most influential business innovators in Denver, May 4. Register Now " Prince, a pioneering musician and creative, died today at 57. This game-changing artist merged his special take on funk and rock into 39 albums, creating classics such as Purple Rain and Little Red Corvette.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/f82bbbcf6c1a7fb1116234d47a5656ca64c6d538.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://www.entrepreneur.com/article/274499</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">9675a9c5-4307-4e65-81aa-7a3332748197</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2016 16:39:14 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[So Now We Know How C-3PO Got His Red Arm In The Force Awakens]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>So Now We Know How C-3PO Got His Red Arm In The Force Awakens</h1><p>Ladies and gentlemen, our global nightmare is over. After months-nearly five of them in fact-of waiting, Marvel's one-shot comic, revealing just why C-3PO has a red arm for most of The Force Awakens, is finally here. As bizarre as it may sound at first, the final product isn't half bad.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/ff7a99fdf22b973fd7d5ffe88bda91f4fec8e32d.png"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://io9.gizmodo.com/so-now-we-know-how-c-3po-got-his-red-arm-in-the-force-a-1770741572</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">708fb560-472d-43bc-b915-50677371ad8e</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2016 16:39:14 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What it's like to ride in the Tesla Model 3]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>What it's like to ride in the Tesla Model 3</h1><p>HAWTHORNE, California - I've had a terrible flu all week. My body aches, my head is pounding, and my throat feels like it might fall out of my neck. Right now, though, I'm riding in the Tesla Model 3, one of the most hotly anticipated cars in the world...</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/7072e2c8eecfad7b01c2532650be669c8647d676.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://mashable.com/2016/04/01/tesla-model-3-first-ride/#GmuWjVf0GZqo</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">178971f8-65f3-42d8-8925-39ef473ad722</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2016 16:39:14 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sevenhugs' Smart Remote]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Sevenhugs' Smart Remote</h1><p>Looking to simplify the endless number of apps and interfaces used to control smart-home products, French start-up Sevenhugs has introduced the first "contextually aware" universal Smart Remote. In other words, it's the first remote to understand where it is in your home and what it's pointing at, allowing users to simply point and click to control devices instead of switching between apps.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/df1caa77bd36920224edf22d445e863c5b829e80.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.coolhunting.com/tech/sevenhugs-smart-remote</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">7ea38763-d774-412d-b997-8a2e5ed7b4b4</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2016 16:39:14 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Travel Smarter: The Backpack That Doubles as a Mobile Office]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Travel Smarter: The Backpack That Doubles as a Mobile Office</h1><p>Our pals at This is Ground recently launched a "smart" backpack that will make you feel like the coolest, most in-the-know traveler out there. Crossing town (or the globe) with a laptop, iPad, headphones, and WiFi port can weigh you down - but it's a reality for many, especially those who work from the road.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/e22f9a492a4d7f602c89eee545449af90da0d5de.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://fathomaway.com/postcards/stuff/this-is-ground-venture-travel-office-backpack/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">ad91f052-35e4-4565-8967-7f65d33a9d66</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2016 16:39:14 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cooling off: TWIG brings Japanese-style cold brewing to London]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Cooling off: TWIG brings Japanese-style cold brewing to London</h1><p>When self-proclaimed tea fanatic and yoga teacher Iona Carter travelled to Kanazawa, Japan last year, something about their brews seemed extra cool. A local specialty, the process of cold brewing tea inspired Carter to launch her own London-based company, TWIG Teas.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/3d340efa15893cce7423e307478a36c656055568.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.wallpaper.com/lifestyle/twig-brings-japanese-style-cold-brewing-to-london</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">b0e377ad-ebcf-4923-8855-c790044bf1be</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2016 16:39:14 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>